http://www.equipmentemporium.com/index.php/legal/privacy-statement

Great for networking
Need advice? Ask a pro!
Login
Username:
Password:
Remember Me
Forgot your password? |
Forgot your username? |
Register Now
Name:
*
Username:
*
Password:
*
Confirm Password:
*
Email:
*
Confirm email Address:
*
Captcha:
*
Fields marked with an asterisk (*) are required.
07-15-2020 -
If you can’t film a script in the pandemic world, then film a pandemic world...
Read More
COVID-19 and Why you should NOT postpone your college...
05-28-2020 -
The first semester of having to teach online is over. It was a unique experience...
Read More
Seat Warmers - Hot food, bad dailies
02-22-2020 -
The seat warmer trick, Or why to always back up your dailies before the PA...
Email
Your privacy is important to EQE Media & Consulting Group.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that EQE Media & Consulting Group collects, and the ways in which EQE Media & Consulting Group uses that personal information.
EQE Media & Consulting Group will not sell nor provide your information to any third party for the sole purpose of marketing, solicitation, or mass marketing services or products.
Personal information collection
EQE Media & Consulting Group may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:
information about your use of this website
information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website
information about transactions carried out over this website
information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services
any other information that you send to EQE Media & Consulting Group.
Using personal information
EQE Media & Consulting Group may use your personal information to:
administer this website;
personalize the website for you;
enable your access to and use of the website services;
send to you products that you purchase;
supply to you services that you purchase;
send you statements and invoices;
collect payments from you; and
send you marketing communications, only as they directly pertain to this website.
Where EQE Media & Consulting Group discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, EQE Media & Consulting Group may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.
Securing your data
EQE Media & Consulting Group will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
EQE Media & Consulting Group will store all the personal information you provide on secure servers.
Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be  protected by encryption technology.
This website contains Google Analytics tracking which includes Demographics and Interest recording. If you wish to opt-out of any of the following Google Analytics Advertising Features which include, but are not limited to:
Remarketing with Google Analytics
Google Display Network Impression Reporting
DoubleClick Platform integrations
Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
You can do so at any time by installing the official Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, found here.
Cross-border data transfers
Information that EQE Media & Consulting Group collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which EQE Media & Consulting Group operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website may be published on the internet and may be available around the world.
You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.
Updating this statement
EQE Media & Consulting Group may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.
You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
Other websites
This website contains links to other websites.
EQE Media & Consulting Group is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.
Contact  EQE Media & Consulting Group
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or EQE Media & Consulting Group's treatment of your personal information, please contact us via:
email to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
post to EQE Media & Consulting Group, PO Box 950207, Mission Hills CA 91395-0207
This privacy statement
This privacy statement is based on a precedent created by employmentlawcontracts.co.uk and published by freenetlaw.com.
Copyright Notice  |  Legal Disclaimer  |  Privacy Statement  |  Terms of Use
Copyright © 2020 FilmTVsound.com. All Rights Reserved. Designed by JoomlArt.com.
Joomla! is Free Software released under the GNU General Public License.
Powered by T3 Framework
